Finding Aid for the Mark Weber Jazz Collection, 1970-2005
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Photographs, Series 3.
  - Artists, Subseries 3.; 258 photographs
    - Cleveland, Jimmy, 1926-, 1979-1981, inclusive; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Taken at the Hollywood Bowl, John Anson Ford Theatre, and the Local 47 Union Hall. Also pictured; Bill Berry Big Band, Jim Hughart, Jackie Kelso, Janet Cleveland, Harry Howard, and Lonny Morgan.
    - Cline, Alex and Nels, 1956-, 1970-1983, inclusive; B&W 11x14, 8x10 and 5x7 and color snapshots (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Taken at such venues as, Century city Playhouse. Also pictured; Eric Von Essen, Jeff Gauthier
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Golia, Vinny and Series 3: Subseries 4, Vinny Golia Large Ensemble. Box 36 for 11x14 prints.
    - Cobb, Jimmy, 1929-, 1979 February 23; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Taken at Bridges Auditorium in Claremont, Ca.
    - Coker, Dolo, 1927-1983, 1980 May 15 and December 28; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Taken at venues such as the University of California, Los Angeles and a KKGO broadcast. Also pictured; Bob Cooper and Harry Sweets Edison.
    - Coleman, Ornette, 1930-, 1981-1986, inclusive; B&W 8x10 and color snapshots (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Taken at such venues as; the Hollywood Bowl in Los Angeles and San Francisco Also pictured; Ornette Coleman, poet David Henderson, George Sams, Joe Zawinal
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Coleman, Ornette.
    - Corea, Chick, 1941-, 1979 June 10; B&W 8x10 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Taken at Blue Mitchell's memorial held at Musicians Union Local 47. Also pictured, Victor Feldman.
    - Cosby, Bill, 1937-, 1982 June 19 and undated; Color Snapshot and B&W 8x10 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Taken at the Playboy Jazz Festival, Cosby was master of ceremonies.
    - Covelli, Larry, 1981 March 29; B&W 8x10 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      Taken in Cucamonga, Ca. Also pictured; Conte Candoli, Joe Romano, and Frank Strazzeri.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Conte Candoli Sextet.
    - Crawford, Ray, 1924-1997, 1980; B&W 11x14, 8x10, and 5x7 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, H.Ray Crawford Quartet and Ray Crawford Quartet. See also Box 36 for 11x14. Also known as H. Ray Crawford.
    - Crayton, Pee Wee, 1914-1985, 1976-1977, inclusive; B&W 8x10 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      Taken at Roy's Rib Inn in Compton, Slones Lounge in Los Angeles. Also pictured; Hoppy Hopkins, Evans Walker. Includes photos autographed by Crayton.
      See Also: Series 3: Subseries 4, Pee Wee Crayton & His Ultimates of Soul.
    - Crayton, Pee Wee, 1914-1985, 1976-1977, inclusive; B&W 5x7 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      See also; Series 3: Subseries 4, Pee Wee Crayton & His Ultimates of Soul.
    - Crothers, Connie, 1941-, 2001-2004, inclusive; Color Snapshots (Box 7, Folder 24)
      Taken in Albuquerque and Cruther's studio in New York City. Also pictured; Ratzo Harris, Roger Mancusco, David Parlato, Janet Simon and Richard Tabnik.
    - Crouch, Stanley, 1945-, 1979 October 20; B&W 8x10 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      Taken in Los Angeles.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3; Bradford, Carter. See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Black Music Infinity.
    - Crowley, Robert, 1981 January 27; B&W 8x10 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      Taken at United Western Studios. Also pictured; Gary Bias, George Bohanon, Jeff Clayton, B.J. Crowley, and "Jiggs" Wilbert Helmsley.
      See also; Series 3: Subseries 4, Robert Crowley Orchestra.
    - Cutler, Chris, 1947-, 2000 November 11; Color Snapshots (Box 7, Folder 27)
      Also pictured, Thomas Dimuzio.
    - Darensbourg, Joe, 1906-1985, 1981 August 4; Color Snapshot (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Taken at MacArthur Park, Los Angeles. Also pictured; Ray Hall, Gideon Honore, Nappy Lamare, Eugene Lebeaux, Phil Stevens, and Bill Stumpp.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Dixie Flyers.
    - Davern, Kenny, 1935-, 2002-2004, inclusive; B&W and Color snapshots 3x5 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Taken in New Mexico at Davern's studio and home in Sandia Park, KUNM radio station in Abuquerque, and Santa Fe. Also pictured; Howard Alden, James Chirillo, Greg Cohen, Elsa Davern, Tony DeNicloa, Matt Domber (of Arbors Records), David Parlato, Andy Poling, Roswell Rudd, and Mark Weber
      See also Series 3; Subseries 4, Kenny Davern Quartet
    - Deane, J.A., 1955-, 1995-2004; B&W and Color snapshots 3x5 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Also pictured; Quincy Adams (engineer for Zerx Records),Brett Leake, Myra Melford,Todd Moore, Michael Vlatkovichand Simon Welter.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Out of Context
    - DeLaRosa, Frank, 1979 March 16; B&W 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Conte Condoli Sextet.
    - Denio, Amy. 1961-, 2000 July 23; Color snapshots (Box 8, Folder 5)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Feder, Janet.
    - Dill, Stefan, 1996-2004, inclusive; Color and B&W snapshots and 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Taken in Abuquerque, New Mexico and San Francisco. Also pictured; Micci Dill (wife), Andy Squire
      Also known as Mustafa Stefan Dill. See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Stefan Dill Trio.
    - Diorio, Joe, 1936-, 1977 April 25; B&W 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Taken at Donte's Jazz Club, Los Angeles, Ca.
    - Dixon, Eric, 1930-, 1979 February 17; BxW 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      With Count Basie Orchestra
    - Edwards, Teddy, 1924-2003, 1980 July 5; BxW 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Photograph autographed by Teddy Edwards.
    - Escheté, Ron, 1948-, 1980-1982; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Also pictured, Mundell Lowe and Dave Pike.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Dave Pike Quintet.
    - Eskelin, Ellery, 1959-, 2000 November 6; Color snapshots (Box 8, Folder 10)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Ellery Eskelin Trio.
    - Evans, Bill, 1929-1980, 1977 May 11; B&W 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Farrell, Joe, 1937-1986, 1984 and undated; B&W 8x10 and color snapshot (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Taken at the Chateau Laurier in Ottawa, Canada and at the Playboy Jazz Festival in Los Angeles, Ca. Also pictured, Bill Cosby.
    - Farris, Lonnie, Rev., 1977 August 28; B&W 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      Also pictured, Rev. Keyes
    - Farris, Lonnie, Rev., 1977 August 28; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Also pictured, Rev,. Keyes
    - Farris, Lonnie, Rev., circa 1979; Color 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      Taken at Rev. Farris's home in Los Angeles, Ca.
    - Feder, Janet, 1999-2003, inclusive; Color Snapshots (Box 8, Folder 17)
      Also pictured; Amy Denio and Janet Simon (Mark Weber's wife).
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Denio, Amy.
    - Ferguson, Sherman, 1944-2006, 1983 June 7; B&W 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Ferris, Glenn, 1950-, 1979 April 14 and undated; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Bradford, Carter.
    - Filano, Ken, 1997 May 25; Color Snapshot (Box 8, Folder 20)
      Note on verso, "Working with Color."
    - Fischer, Clare, 1928-, 1980 June 8; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      Taken at the Baked Potato in Los Angeles, Ca. Also pictured, Gary Foster.
    - Flahive, Larry, 1980 June 22; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      Taken at Gilberto's in Cucamonga, Ca. Also pictured, Charlie Shoemaker.
    - Flynn, Justine, 1996 April 27; B&W Snapshots (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Foley, George, 1987 May 22; Color Snapshots (Box 8, Folder 24)
      Taken in Cleveland, Ohio at the Standard Oil Building Atrium.
    - Foster, Gary, 1936-, 1980 April 19; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Gary Foster Quintet
    - Franklin, Henry, 1940-, 1977 February 7; B&W 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      Also known as, "The Skipper."
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Gene Russell Trio.
    - Frishberg, Dave, 1933-, 1980 and undated; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      Taken at Two Dollar Bills, Hollywood and John Anson Ford Theater (?), Los Angeles. Also pictured; Bob Badgely, Monty Budwig, Nick Ceroli, Jimmy Cleveland, Bob Cooper, Al Ceechi, Jimmy Cleveland and Bob Hardaway.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Hardaway, Bob.
    - Fulson, Lowell, 1921-1999, 1981; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      Taken in Claremont, California.
    - Gales, Larry, 1936-1995, 1977 July 18; B&W 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Gburek, Jeff, 1963-, 2004 July 11; B&W snapshots (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Gill, Lisa, 2003 February 24; Color Snapshots (Box 8, Folder 35)
      Note on verso, "poet."
    - Gladden, Eddie, 1937-2003, 1983 June 19; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      Taken at the Hollywood Bowl in Los Angeles, California.
    - Goldsmith, George, 1980 August 6; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      Taken at Howard Rumsey's Lighthouse in Hermosa beach, california. Also pictured; Larry Gales, Billy Hinton, and Horace Tapscott. Includes photograph autographed by Larry Gales.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3; Gales, Larry and Tapscott, Horace.
    - Golia, Vinny, 1946-, 1980-1982; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      Also pictured; Wayne Peet and John Rapson.
      Other source lists D.O.B. as 1956. See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Vinny Golia Large Ensemble.
    - Golia, Vinny, 1946-, 1977-1982; B&W 11x14, 5x7 and color snapshots (Box 8, Folder 39)
      Taken at Studio Z in Los Angeles; Spectrum Studios in Venice Beach, Los Angeles; University of California Los Angeles and in Albuquerque, New Mexico. (UCLA). Also pictured; Tim Berne, Rob Blaleslee, John Carter, Alex Cline, Ken Filiano, John Fumo, Charles Hall, Billy Mintz, Roberto Miranda, Wynell Montgomery, Wayne Peet, and Michael Vlatkovitch.
      Other source lists D.O.B. as 1956. See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Carter, Cline, Miranda, Vlatkovitch. Series 3: Subseries 4, Jasmine and Vinny Golia Large Ensemble. Box 36 for 11x14 prints.
    - Goodman, Benny, 1909-1986, undated; B&W 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Taken at the Hollywood Bowl, Los Angeles, California.
    - Gordon, Dexter, 1923-1990, 1976-1983; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Taken at Howard Rumsey's Lighthouse, Hermosa Beach, Califonia; Also pictured; Claremont, California; Hollywood Bowl, Los Angeles. Eddie Gladden, Kirk Lightsey, Rufus Reid, Woody Shaw, Lamar Wright, Jr.,
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Gladden, Eddie and Reid, Rufas.
    - Graver, Joanne, 1980 April 18 and 23; B&W 11x14, 8x10, and 5x7 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Also pictured, Bob Badgely, Al Cheechi and Don Preston.
      See also Box 36 for 11x14 print.
    - Green, Freddie, 1911-1987, 1979 February 17; B&W 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Photo autographed by Freddie Green.
    - Griffin, Curtis, undated; B&W 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Publicity still embossed with title, "Consolidated Productions Curtis Green." Photographer unknown.
    - Gruntfest, John, 1978 August 18 and 19; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Taken at Pangea, San Francisco. Also pictured, Harry Kuntz and Loren Means.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Kuntz, Harry and Series 3: Subseries 4, Full Moon Ritual Band
    - Guralnick, Tom, 1951-, 1995-2000; B&W 8x10, B&W and color snapshots (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Taken in Albuquerque, New Mexico. Also pictured; Stefen Dill, Steve Feld, Von Freeman, Reggie Gammon, Bud Shank, Mrs. Shank, Jefferson Voorhees and Mark Weber.
      Includes publicity photograph. See also Series: 3 Subseries 3, Dill, Stefen; Lacy, Steve; Weber, Mark and Series 3: Subseries 4, Tom Guralnick Trio.
    - Haden, Charlie, 1937-, 1980; B&W 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Also pictured, Lew Tabackin and Joey Baron.
    - Hamm, Jimmy, 2000 November 4; Color Snapshots (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Hardaway, Bob, 1928-, 1979 May 27; B&W 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Taken at Donte's in Los Angeles, California. Also pictured; Bob Cooper and Dave Pell.
    - Harris, Billy, 1980 April 29; B&W 8x10, 5x7 and color snapshots (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Taken in Los Angeles and Venice Beach, Ca. Also pictured; Tom Alback and Horace Tapscott.
    - Haynes, Roy, 1926-, 1997 and 1980; B&W 8x10 and color snapshot (Box 9, Folder 13)
      8x10 taken 1980 July 30 at the Hollywood Bowl, Clarence Johnston also pictured. Snapshot taken 1997 November 17 in Albuquerque, NM.
    - Heard, John, 1938-, undated; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Taken during Nimbus recording session on Sunset Blvd., Los Angeles, Ca. Also pictured; Gary Bias on alto sax, Ricky Kelly on vibes, Nate Morgan on piano, Roberto Miranda on bass, and Fritz Wise on drums.
    - Heath, Jimmy, 1926-, Circa late 1970's; B&W 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Autographed by Jimmy Heath.
    - Heath, Percy, 1923-2005, Circa late 1970's; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Helm, Bob, 1914-2002, undated; B&W 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Hemphill, Julius, 1938?-1995, 1977 September 11; B&W 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Taken in Los Angeles, Ca. Also pictured, E.J. Carroll.
    - Hemphill, Julius, 1938?-1995, 1977; B&W 5x7 and color 11x14 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Taken in Los Angeles and at the Century City Playhouse in Los Angeles. Also pictured; Baikida E.J Carroll, Alex Cline.
      See also Box 35 for color 11x14.
    - Heyl, Kurt, 2003, 2005; color snapshots (Box 9, Folder 20)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured; Mathew David on drums, Kurt Heyl on trombone, Sara Schoenbeck on bassoon, Mark Weaver on tuba, and Ben Wright on bass.
    - Higgins, Billy, 1936-2001, 1977 and 1984; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Taken 1977 May 5 at Howard Rumsey's Lighthouse in Hermosa Beach, Ca. Also pictured; Art Farmer, Sam Jones and Cedar Walton. Taken 1984 September 23 at the Watts Tower Festival. Also pictured, Papa Jo Jones.
    - Hill, Linda, 1980 April 25; B&W 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      Also pictured; Tom Albach, Everett brown Jr., and Roberto Miranda
    - Holloway, Red, 1927-, 1981-1982; B&W and blue 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      Also pictured; Curtis Peagler, Jerome Richardson and Phillip Upchurch.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Witherspoon, Jimmy.
    - Hooker, John Lee, 1915?-2001, 1976 July 8; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Taken in Fullerton, Ca. Also pictured, Ron Thompson.
    - Howard, Harold, 1980 and 1983; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Taken 1980 in Pomona. Taken 1983 June 18 at the Hollywood Bowl in Los Angeles, Ca., also pictured, Karen Barron, Bobby Brooks, Herbie Hancock, Clarence Johnston, Charlie Rouse, Gerald Wilson, Lamar Wright, Jr. and Snooky Young.
    - Hucko, Peanuts, 1918-2003, 1981 August 9; color snapshots (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Taken at MacArthur Park in Los Angeles. Also pictured Chuck Anderson, Bob Higgins, Manny Klein, Eddie Miller, Dick Shanahan, Ray Sherman, and David Stone.
    - Hurst, Robert, 1964-, 2002 March 20 and 21; color 5x7 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      Taken in Taos, NM and West Spanish Peak, Colorado. Also pictured Geri Allen and Billy Hart.
    - Jackson, Milt, 1923-1999, 1979 May 3; B&W 5x7 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Taken at Howard Rumsey's Lighthouse in Hermosa Beach, Ca. Also pictured; Monty Alexander and Andrew Simpkins.
    - James, Etta, 1938-, 1979 October 14; B&W 11x14 (Box 36)
      Taken at Johnny Otis' church.
    - Jenkins, Leroy, 2001 June 25; Color snapshots (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Also pictured, Steve Lacy.
    - Johnson, Foster, Circa 1980; Taken backstage at the Playboy Jazz Festival at the Hollywood Bowl, Los Angeles. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Jimmy, 1928-, 1987 May 2; Color snapshots (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Philly Joe, 1923-1985, 1980 April 9; B&W 8x10 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Taken at Donte's 4269 Lankersheim Blvd. in North Hollywood, Los Angeles. Also pictured; Ralh Bowen, Andy McKee and Jack Wilson.
    - Kaplan, Lee, 1978 November 25; B&W 5x7 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Also pictured Margarette Shuette.
    - Katz, Fred, 1918-, 1979, 1981; B&W 11x14, 8x10, and 5x7 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Some taken in Fullerton, Ca. Also pictured; Buddy Collette, Jerry Hagen, Hyman Katz, Althea B. McLaren (sculptor) and Father James Perrone.
    - Kelly, Rickey, Circa 1970; B&W 8x10 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Keppeler, Ken, 2000, 2004; Color and B&W snapshots (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured, Jeanie McLerie.
    - Kikowski, Dave, 1997 November 17; Color snapshots (Box 10, Folder 13)
      Taken in Abuquerque, New Mexico. Also pictured; Tom Guralnick and Ed Howard.
    - Kollektief, Willem Breuker, 2000 March 30; B&W snapshots (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM.
    - Kriuda, Ernie, 1987 June 20; color 3x5 snapshots (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Also pictured, Chip Stephans.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Ernie Kriuda Quartet.
    - Kuntz, Henry, 1977 August 24; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      Taken at the George Sand Bookstore in Los Angeles. Also pictured; Henry Kaiser and Laurel Sprigg.
    - LaBeef, Sleepy, 1935-, 1990 July 17; B&W 8x10 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      Taken at the Zephyr Club.
    - Lacy, Steve, 1934-2004, circa 1954, 2000-2003; B&W and color snapshots (Box 10, Folder 18)
      Taken in Albuquerque and Santa Fe, NM. Also pictured; Irene Aebi, JJ Avenal, John Betsh, and George Lewis. 1954 dated photo of a snapshot of Steve Lacy and Kenny Davern.
      See also Series 3:Subseries 4, Steve Lacy Trio and Quintet.
    - Lake, Oliver, 1942-, 1977-1978, 1980; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Taken at such venues as Century City Playhouse. Also pictured; John Carter and James Newton.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Carter, John.
    - Land, Harold, 1928-2001, 1976-1977, 1981, 1983, 1985; Color 11x14 and snapshots (Box 10, Folder 20)
      Taken at such venues as Beverly Cavern, Cal Poly, Donte's, John Anson Ford Theater. Also pictured; Martin Banks, Tony Dumas, Freddie Hill, Bobbie Hutcherson, Rickey Kelly, Herbie Lewis, Gildo Mahones, Warne Marsh, Blue Mitchell, Nolan Smith, and Fritz Wise.
      See also Box 35 for 11x17.
    - Lawrence, Doug, 1956-, 2004 February 27; Color snapshot (Box 10, Folder 21)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM in front of 725.
    - Leake, Brent, 1996 August 19; Color snapshot (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Leviev, Milcho, 1937-, Circa late 1970's; B&W 8x10 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Taken at Donte's in North Hollywood, Ca.
    - Levy, Lou, 1928-2001, 1979-1981, inclusive; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      Taken at such venues as Donte's in North Hollywood, Gilberto's in Cucamonga, Ca. Also pictured Dick Berk, Jim DeJulio, Larry Flahive, Plas Johnson, Larry Morgan, Jack Nimitz, Andrew Simpkins and Jack Sheldon.
    - Lewis, Herbie, 1941-, undated; B&W 8x10 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Lincoln, Abby, 1930-, 1980 July 31; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      Taken in Los Angeles, Ca. Also pictured, Barbara Pelletier.
    - Lindberg, John, 1979-September-31; B&W 11x14 (Box 36)
    - Littlefield, Patti, 1996 September 15; Color snapshot (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Lockwood, Robert, 1915-, 1986 July 23; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Taken in Cleveland, OH.
    - Lowe, Frank, 1943-2003, 1976 July 2; B&W 8x10 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      Also pictured; Tylon Barea, F. Lowe, Butch Morris and James Newton.
    - Lowe, Mundell, 1922-, 1982 October 9; B&W 8x10 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      Also pictured, Bill Perkins
    - Lytton, Paul, 2003 May 5; Color snapshot (Box 10, Folder 30)
      Taken at Outpost in albuquerque, NM. Also pictured, Evan Parker and Alex von Schlippenbach.
    - Mackay, Dave, 1932-, 2004 May 28; Color snapshot (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Also pictured; Ted Brown, Mark Feber, Lee Konitz, and Derek Oles.
    - Mackay, Dave, 1932-, 2004 May 28; Color snapshot (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Mann, Herbie, 1930-, 2000 May 15; Color snapshot (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Taken at Outpost in Albuquerque, NM.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Sona Terra.
    - Manno, Jack, 2002 May 4; B&W snapshots (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Marsalis, Ellis, 1934-, 1982; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Taken in New Orleans, LA.
    - Marsalis, Wynton, 1961-, 1983 June 18; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Taken at the Playboy Jazz Festival at the Hollywood Bowl, Los Angeles, Ca.
    - Marsh, Warne, 1927-1987, 1976-1977, 1980, 1985; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 and color snapshots. (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Also pictured; Alan Broadbent, Gary Foster and Art Pepper.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Land and Pepper.
    - Mateen, Sabir, undated; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Also known as "Sabia" and surname misspelled as "Matteen." See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.)
    - McCann, Les, 1935-, 1979 July 7; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Taken at the Watts Towers Jazz Festival. Also pictured, David Williams.
    - McHargue, Rosy, 1909-1999, 1982 August 22; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Taken at McArthur Park in Los Angeles, Ca.
    - McKenzie, Colin, 2000 October 26; color snapshots (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - McPherson, Charles, 1939-, 1979 October 17; B&W 11x14 (Box 36)
    - Menza, Don, 1936-, 1979-1981; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Taken at such venues as Donte's in North Hollywood, Also pictured; Frank De La Rosa, Chuck Findley, Bill Reickenbach
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, De La Rosa. See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Don Menza Big Band and Don Menza Quintet.
    - Miles, Long Gone, 1925-1987, 1984 July 15; Color 3x5 snapshots (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Taken at the Watts Towers Jazz festival in Los angeles, Ca. Also pictured; Freddie Clark, Jummy Hines, Bob Lucas and Bernie Pearl.
    - Mintz, Billy, 1947-, 1997 May 25; Color 3x5 snapshots (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Taken in Abuquerque, NM.
    - Miranda, Roberto, 1980-1981,1984; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 and color snapshots (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Taken at such venues as the Century City Playhouse, Gon-Bop Drum Factory, Hollywood Bowl in Los Angeles and the Lobero Theater in Santa Barbara, Ca. Also pictured; Red Callendar, Bill Cosby, Eric Von Essen, Virgil Figuero, Linda Hill, Harold Howard, and Sabir Mateen.
      Photograph autographed by Red Callendar. See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Cosby, Tapscott. Series 3: Subseries 4, Pan Afrikan Peoples, Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Sonship.
    - Moore, Eddie, 1940-, 1981 February 14; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      Taken in San Francisco, Ca. Also pictured, Russell Baba.
    - Moore, Todd, 1996 May 11; Color 3x5 snapshots (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Morgan, Nate, undated; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      Taken during the Nimbus recording session.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Heard and Tapscott.
    - Mulligan, Gerry, 1927-1996, Circa late 1970's; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Taken at the Hollywood Bowl in Los Angeles, Ca.
    - Murray, David, 1955-, 1977; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Taken at such venues as the Century City Playhouse, Claremont Colleges. Also pictured; John Carter, Oliver Johnson, Roberto Miranda, James Newton, and Monica Pecot.
      See also Series 3: Suberies 3; Carter, Newton, and Series 3: Subseries 4, Black Music Infinity and David Murray Trio.
    - Musselwhite, Charlie, 1944-, 1980 February 25; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Also pictured, Mike Watson (aka. Junior Watson).
    - Neidlinger, Buell, 1936-, 1976 September 18; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      Also pictured; Deborah Fuss and Don Preston.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, El Monte Art Ensemble.
    - Newton, James, 1976-1977; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Taken at such venues as the Claremont Colleges. Also pictured Tylon Barea, John Carter, Glenn Ferris, and David Murray.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3; Bradford, Carter, Lowe, Murray. Series 3: Subseries 4, James Newton Quartet.
    - Oliver, James, 1984 June 16; Color snapshots (Box 11, Folder 26)
      Taken at the Hollywood Bowl Playboy Jazz Festival.
    - Ostertag, Bob, 1997 September 23; Color snapshots (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Otis, Johnny, 1921-, 1985 September 29; B&W snapshots (Box 11, Folder 28)